Welcome to the Android Basics Nanodegree.
欢迎学习 Android 基础知识纳米学位课程
My name is Chris and I'm a curriculum lead here at Udacity.
我叫 Chris 是优达学城的一名课程负责人
&gt;&gt; And my name is Catherine and I'm a developer advocate at Google.
我叫 Catherine 是 Google 的一名技术推广工程师
&gt;&gt; There are over 1.4 billion active Android devices today.
目前有超过 14 亿台正在使用的 Android 设备
So becoming ian Android developer means being able to build software
成为 Android 开发者也就意味着能够创建
that can reach and impact the lives of tons of users around the world.
面向全世界千千万万名用户的软件 并影响到无数人的生活
&gt;&gt; Yeah, this is a pretty incredible time in history because mobile apps
是的 移动应用正在改变我们的生活和工作方式
are changing the way that we live and work.
这将是一段载入史册的人类发展阶段
So we're super excited that you're taking the first step
非常激动你能够迈出第一步
to becoming a developer.
朝着开发者的方向前进
For this Nanodegree, you don't need any programming experience.
对于此纳米学位课程 你不需要任何编程经验
If you know how to use a computer and a smartphone you're ready to go.
如果你知道如何使用计算机和智能手机 那就足够了
&gt;&gt; Yeah, that's right.
是的
No programming experience needed.
不需要任何编程经验
So if you've ever had an awesome idea for an app but
如果你曾经有过非常棒的应用创意
didn't know how to get started, then this is the program for you.
但是不知道如何开始 那么这门课程就太适合你了
&gt;&gt; We'll walk you through how to build several simple Android apps.
我们将逐步指导你如何构建几个简单的 Android 应用
And along the way you'll learn the Java programming language.
在此期间 你将学会 Java 编程语言
And also some key computer science concepts.
还有一些关键的计算机科学概念
&gt;&gt; Yeah, we're going to focus on what's important and
我们将侧重于一些重要内容
how to directly apply what you've learned to the apps you're building.
讲解如何将所学的知识直接运用到正在创建的应用中
&gt;&gt; It's going to be challenging and that's expected.
这门课程会充满挑战 这是正常现象
But that's why we're going to teach you how to think like a developer.
这是因为我们将指导你如何像开发者一样思考问题
We'll explain the decisions that arise when building an app.
我们将解释在构建应用中做出的决策
You'll learn how to read documentation, search for online resources,
你将学习如何阅读文档 搜索在线资源
plan out your tests.
为测试做准备
And also figure out how to get unstuck.
以及如何解决疑难问题 走出困境
&gt;&gt; And signature to every Nanodegree experience,
和每门纳米学位课程一样
you'll also have the opportunity to complete projects on your own.
你将有机会自行完成项目
And get invaluable feedback on your code.
并针对自己的代码获得宝贵的反馈
&gt;&gt; And by the end of the program, you'll have completed a whole portfolio of apps
学完这门课程后 你将完成整个应用作品集
that you can share with your family and friends.
你可以向自己的亲朋好友展示这些作品集
&gt;&gt; We hope that you become inspired to learn more and
希望你能受到激励 继续深入学习
go on to build some great apps.
并构建一些很棒的应用
&gt;&gt; Yeah, let's go get started.
我们开始吧
&gt;&gt; Let's do it.
好的
[SOUND]
[声音]